Yaichi.
Toyoyaki.
Issao.
Ryosuke.
Yukio.
Kaikaido.
Tuan Ubuyashiki, saatnya untuk kembali.
Tubuh Anda akan kewalahan.
Saya tidak tahu berapa
kali saya bisa kembali ke pemakaman ini.
Semua penyesalan anak muda ini
Saya berharap ini berakhir sebelum saya pergi.
Baru bulan ini
laporan korban yang disebabkan oleh setan
telah meningkat tujuh kali lipat.
Anak-anak saya dari Demon Slayer Corp.
Sekarang, kali ini
memimpin serangan melawan iblis.
Tidak peduli berapa banyak nyawa berharga yang diambil iblis.
Keinginan yang kuat
tidak pernah bisa diambil.
Tidak peduli seberapa besar hitnya
mereka akan tetap berdiri dan bertarung lagi.
Baiklah, ayo sembunyikan pedang kita dan naik kereta.
Oh tidak!
Kereta akan berangkat!
Apa polisi sudah pergi?
Meski mereka masih di sini,
kita masih harus naik kereta.
Ha ha! Pertarungan! Pemilik tanah!
Bodoh itu!
Ayo pergi!
Jangan tinggalkan aku!
Tunggu! Tunggu aku!
Piring! Inosuke!
Zenitsu!
Sangat cepat!
Maaf maaf.
Berhenti main-main!
Kemari, idiot!
Hei!
Nenek, apakah ini tidak apa-apa?
Terima kasih untuk bantuannya.
Aku sangat menyesal...
Apa?
Jangan khawatir tentang itu!
Di mana pria yang seharusnya bertemu dengan kita,
Hashira, kan?
Apa kamu tahu seperti apa dia?
Dia seharusnya sangat kurang ajar.
Saya juga ingat bau ashe.
Saya pikir saya melihatnya sebelumnya.
Film Pembunuh Setan: Kereta Tak Terbatas
Lezat!
Orang itu adalah Hashira?
Dia jelas bukan orang biasa ...
Lezat!
Maaf, maaf mengganggu ...
Rengoku ...
Lezat!
Saya pikir ini sudah cukup jelas ...
Kaulah yang dulu bersama Master Ubuyashiki.
Iya.
Saya Kamado Tanjiro.
Orang-orang ini juga anggota dari Demon Slayer Corp.
Ini adalah teman-temanku-
ini Zenitsu dan
di sebelahnya adalah seorang pria bernama Inosuke!
Baik.
Konon, iblis di dalam kotak itu adalah ...
Ya, itu adikku, Nezuko.
Setan saat itu
menunjukkan sesuatu yang disetujui oleh Guru.
Kami dalam hal ini bersama-sama.
Ayo, duduk.
Luar biasa!
Perut Pemiliknya luar biasa!
Berhenti, kamu akan memecahkan kaca!
Harap coba aman!
Kenapa kamu di kereta ini?
Apakah kamu punya misi?
Kami menerima pesanan dari Gagak.
Kami diberitahu bahwa korban dari Kereta Tak Terbatas terus meningkat.
Kami diperintahkan ke tempat ini terjadi.
Untuk bertemu denganmu secepat mungkin.
Jadi, ternyata begini.
Oke!
Iya.
Saya ingin menanyakan satu hal lagi ...
Saya ingin bertanya sendiri.
Apa masalahnya?
Katakan padaku.
Ini tentang ayahku.
Apa yang terjadi dengan ayahmu?
Dia selalu lemah dan sakit.
Lemah dan sakit?
Walaupun demikian...
... di salju yang cukup untuk membekukan paru-paru
dia akan melakukan tarian Kagura sepanjang malam.
Beruntung sekali!
Sehingga-
Apa itu!
Tarian Dewa Api
dalam skenario hidup dan mati ...
Saya ingat tarian Kagura yang saya lihat ketika saya masih kecil.
Jika Anda tahu sesuatu, Tn. Flame Hashira
Saya berharap Anda bisa memberi tahu saya.
Saya tidak tahu apa-apa!
Ini pertama kalinya aku mendengar tentang Kagura untuk Dewa Api.
Tarian Kagura yang dibawakan oleh ayahmu
bisa digunakan dalam pertempuran.
Itu sangat bagus.
Sepertinya topik ini sudah banyak dibahas.
Maaf, bisakah Anda mengatakan lebih banyak?
Jadilah muridku!
Aku akan menjagamu dengan baik!
Mohon tunggu!
Dimana kamu melihat
Dengan siapa Anda berbicara?
Sungguh orang yang aneh ...
Flame Breathing memiliki sejarah panjang.
Seorang pendekar pedang yang menggunakan Api dan Air
terlepas dari jamannya
harus menjadi Pilar.
Api.
Air.
Angin.
Batu.
Guntur.
Ini adalah bentuk pernapasan utama.
Semua bentuk lainnya
berasal dari cabangnya.
Misalnya, Kabut diturunkan dari Angin.
Pendekar pemula
apa warna pedangmu?
Maaf, nama saya Tanjiro.
Warna pedangku adalah hitam.
Pedang hitam.
Ini masalah besar!
Apakah ini sangat buruk?
Saya belum pernah mendengar itu sebelumnya
seseorang dengan pedang hitam menjadi Pilar.
Sampai hari ini
tidak ada yang pernah mendengar hal seperti itu.
Bentuk apa yang akan menjadi spesialisasi Anda?
Belajarlah dari saya!
Kamu tidak akan kecewa!
Itu bukanlah apa yang saya maksud!
Dan dimana yang kamu lihat?
Dengan siapa Anda berbicara?
Dia aneh
tapi dia juga orang baik yang memperhatikan orang lain.
Dari baunya dia memiliki rasa keadilan yang kuat.
Ini bagus!
Sangat cepat!
Itu berbahaya, bodoh!
Saya ingin keluar dan berlari di sampingnya!
Mari kita lihat siapa yang berlari lebih cepat!
Harus ada batasan untuk kebodohanmu!
Kami berada dalam situasi berbahaya.
Kami tidak tahu kapan iblis akan muncul.
Benarkah itu?
Apakah setan benar-benar muncul di kereta ini?
Mereka punya.
Mereka benar-benar punya?
Saya tidak ingin menjadi seperti itu
di kereta dengan setan!
Ada setan di kereta ini!
Ahhh!
Saya ingin turun!
Dalam waktu singkat
di kereta ini
lebih dari empat puluh orang hilang.
Banyak pendekar pedang telah dikirim ke kereta ini
tapi semuanya hilang.
Sebagai Pilar, saya telah dipanggil untuk menyelidiki.
Kenapa selalu seperti ini!
Saya ingin turun!
Lepaskan aku!
Mohon tunjukkan tiket Anda.
Apa yang dia lakukan?
Konduktor ingin memastikan tiket Anda asli.
Dia akan menandai tiket Anda.
Ini dia...
Apa yang terjadi?
Ada bau yang menjijikkan ...
Terima kasih...
Saya mengkonfirmasi ...
Konduktor-
berbahaya di sini, tolong evakuasi daerah itu.
Situasinya sangat mendesak
tolong tidak keberatan saya membawa pedang.
Anda menggunakan Blood Arts untuk menyembunyikan tubuh besar ini?
Tidak heran sulit untuk mendeteksi Anda.
Tapi
karena Anda berusaha membunuh orang yang tidak bersalah
pedang yang menyala ini di tanganku
akan menghancurkanmu.
Flame Breathing!
Formulir Pertama!
Api Tidak Mengetahui!
Luar biasa!
Dia merawat iblis itu seperti tidak ada apa-apanya!
Ada iblis lain di sini.
Aku datang!
Jangan tinggalkan aku!
Aku tidak akan membiarkanmu menyakiti manusia itu.
Apakah kamu tidak mendengar apa yang baru saja saya katakan?
Lawanmu ada di sini.
Apa-apaan itu?
Tangannya panjang?
Tangannya sangat panjang!
Lihat saya!
Aku duluan!
Tunggu sebentar, masih ada orang yang belum kabur!
Hanya harus membunuh iblis itu dan semuanya baik-baik saja!
The carriage behind us is safe.
Go.
Now there are no problems.
Let's end this quickly.
Flame Breathing!
Second Form!
Rising Scorching Sun!
Too...
He's so strong!
Superb swordsmanship!
Please accept me as a disciple!
Of course, no problem!
I'll train you to become a great swordsman!
I also want-
Okay, I'll take all three of you!
Rengoku is our teacher!
Teacher!
Teacher...!
I did as you ordered!
I cut the ticket and let them fall asleep!
Please!
Let me go to sleep!
Please let me meet my dead wife and daughter!
Please!
Please...
Okay.
You've done very well...
Fall asleep...
Have a dream of meeting your family.
Your Grace...
what should we do?
Wait a while, they will fall asleep.
Wait here before that.
These are intelligent demon slayers.
Sometimes when a person with murderous intent draws close
they will wake up again unconsciously.
When you get close enough to tie the rope
be careful not to touch them.
Because of where these demon slayers are
I can't leave the front carriage.
Before I am ready
perform your duties well.
All that matters is to dream of happiness.
Yes.
What happened... what happened?
Calm down, calm down.
You must be calm.
It's brother!
Brother, you're back!
Did you sell all of the charcoal?
Brother?
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
To die in a sweet dream...
what a wonderful thing.
Even if it is a powerful demon slayer
there are no exceptions.
The driving force of mankind is the mind...
...and the spirit.
Just destroy the spiritual core
and everything is done.
They are so easy to kill
the human heart is the same no matter who it is.
They are all so fragile
like glass.
The rope should be tied to the wrist.
Is this the right way?
Yes.
Don't forget what he told us.
Breathe slowly.
Count in your heart.
You can fall into deep sleep by doing this.
Three, four, five, six...
Then, my brother burst into tears!
It shocked me!
He's so strange!
Maybe it’s because I’m too tired.
No need to make a fuss.
I'm fine.
Did you catch a cold?
Do you have a fever?
Don't push yourself.
Rest at home today.
I'm really fine.
Are you really okay?
Would you like to make a dumpling?
Stop playing around!
Really?
If you don't like it just say so!
I feel like I was having a nightmare.
Go to sleep, sleep quietly.
Forget breathing, sleep quietly.
Even if a demon comes, sleep quietly.
Sleep quietly even in your heart.
They seem very happy.
They should all be having pleasant dreams.
Fall gently.
Fall into a dream.
Fall into a deep sleep.
I can't wake up from my dream anymore.
Come here!
The peaches here are delicious.
They're blooming with white clover flowers.
I will make a beautiful wreath for you.
I really know how to make wreaths.
How about it, Nezuko?
I'd like to make a lot of them!
Zenitsu!
There's a small river half-way
but don't worry, it's very shallow!
Small river?
Zenitsu, I don't know...
I was never taught how to swim.
It's okay!
Just hop on my back and we'll both cross!
It's just a small river!
I won't allow any water to get on Nezuko!
Leave everything to me!
Just leave it to me!
Look at me!
Expedition team!
Cave expedition team!
We are the cave expedition team!
Discovery team!
Boss!
What's the matter?
Tell me, what did you find?
(Tanjiro)
There is a very strong smell of the cave owner!
Bump!
(Zenitsu)
I also heard him screaming, tweeting!
Really?
In this place?
Okay, let's go to battle!
Obey, boss!
What are you doing?
Don't go ahead, fight as three!
Come here!
Look!
I give you bright acorns!
Do you see?
Attack!
What am I here for?
That's right.
Report to my Father.
To become a Pillar.
What's so great about being alive?
It's all boring.
It's not my business.
Anyway, it doesn't matter if it's you or me.
Everyone does what they can to get ahead.
Older brother!
Is Father happy for you?
If I become like you
will father also recognize me?
He didn't used to be like that.
Father could have been a Pillar of the Demon Slayer Corp.
He was originally a passionate person.
Then one day, he suddenly gave up.
Suddenly.
The one who did his best
who was passionate and nurtured us.
Why?
Don't think about things that you can't change.
I still feel sorry for Senjuro.
His mother who died of illness
that he has no memory of.
There's nothing he can do about that.
To be honest with you,
Father is not happy for me.
He doesn't care about me.
However,
your older brother will not lose his enthusiasm because of this.
The flame in my heart never goes out.
I will never become frustrated.
Senjuro,
you are different from me.
You have your older brother.
And he believes in his younger brother.
No matter which way you go,
you can become a great person.
Have a burning passion in your heart!
You have to work hard to live!
Don't lose faith!
Ah, this feels good.
Those ropes I made
allow someone to invade the dream of the person tied to it.
It's a special technique.
In every circumstance
I face the enemy very carefully.
Just fall asleep.
Whether they are great or insignificant
they will be like babies.
A delicious meal.
I just have to wait for those demon slayers to be dealt with...
...taste slowly.
No need to swing the sword so rigidly.
Relax your shoulders.
The power resides in your shoulders.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's dangerous over there, that's the master of the body.
I have to be careful not to be found by him.
Find the boundary of the dream.
Faster!
The dreams I make are not endless
but centered on the dreamer.
A circle appears around the master of the body.
Beyond the dream is a special field without consciousness.
The spiritual core is hidden there.
Your job is to destroy the core.
In this way, the owner of the dreamland
will become a waste.
Found it!
Although the scenery continues...
I can't move forward.
I must quickly destroy the spiritual core of this person.
I also have a dream to make myself happy.
What a strange unconsciousness
it's so hot.
It's actually burning.
Have to hurry.
Finally found it!
Is this the spiritual core?
Seeing this for the first time.
I just have to destroy it...
...then I can!
When people fall into this sleep
they shouldn't be able to move at all!
How is this possible?
What an amazing survival instinct!
Tanjiro.
Today, Mother is going to make your favorite food.
I'm sure you'll like it!
Wait, I'll mash the leftover mochi right away.
Awesome!
Mother wants to bake senbei!
Not fair!
I also like senbei!
We're brothers, you know?
I would also like some senbei!
Me too!
So
let's eat together!
Can you help your mother get the cooking net?
Yes!
I will mash the mochi with a grinder!
Oh, look the beggar is here to help!
I also want to help!
You're gonna be held responsible for eating that later!
What a thief!
Nezuko, let's go.
What did I just say?
I'm back!
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Welcome back, brother.
Huh, where is Nezuko?
Sister just went to the mountain to pick wild vegetables.
It's daytime!
Is that not okay?
Is that...
Strange.
Tanjirou, can you boil the bath water for me?
The kitchen is still busy for now.
I'm saying strange things.
Is it because I'm tired?
Strange, it disappeared.
What happened just now?
I seemed to have... seen a box?
An illusion caused by the snow?
Wake up soon!
Wake up!
Wake up soon, everyone is attacked!
It's a dream, this is just a dream!
Wake up soon!
That's it!
Yeah, I'm...
I should be on the train!
Wake up and fight!
Hurry up and fight!
Fight fast!
Brother, can you give me your pickled radish?
Just say no!
You can't do this every time!
Why is it always like this!
Grabbing something from brother!
You're annoying!
You already have another bowl of rice!
I didn't wake up.
I didn't wake up!
I'm still in the dream!
What do I have to do to leave?
I just figured out this is a dream!
What do I do?
I have to wake up!
Brother!
You're catching on fire!
It's the smell of Nezuko.
Nezuko is bleeding!
My demon slayer uniform.
I'm aware now.
Waking up little by little.
What happened?
Brother, are you okay?
Brother?
Sorry... I have to go.
I can't come back.
I'm so sorry.
Brother!
If the demon that made me dream is nearby
you have to find him as soon as possible and get rid of him.
Find out where...
Brother, where are you going?
I picked a lot of wild vegetables on the mountain today.
Mother, over here!
Brother suddenly caught on fire!
Mother?
Tanjiro, are you okay?
Older brother...
What's wrong, Tanjiro?
What is that uniform you're wearing?
I really want to stay in this place forever.
I really want to go back.
If this is real
I will live with everyone like this.
On this mountain.
If this is real
everyone is doing well now.
Nezuko can walk in the sunlight,
walk under the clear sky.
If this is real
I will burn charcoal as usual today.
It would be impossible to have a sword.
If this is real...
But I have lost them.
It's impossible to go back.
Brother, don't you want us!
Brother, don't leave us!
Sorry!
Sorry, Mother!
I can't be with you anymore!
But I will always miss you in my heart!
I will miss each of you!
Thank you for everything...
I wish I could apologize to you all...
I have not forgotten you!
No matter what, you are in my heart!
So please...
Please forgive me!
I must quickly destroy his spiritual core.
Here is his heart.
How can it be so beautiful?
This vast expanse?
So warm...
Where is the spiritual core?
This unconsciousness...
what exactly is going on?
Speaking of which, that crazy boar that makes me feel sick.
What's wrong with him?
Why is he here?
Perverted naked boar!
Dark...
It's so dark you can't see anything.
How annoying.
The unconsciousness of this blonde kid.
It's too ridiculous.
I'll have to use my hands
to find where the spiritual core is?
What a joke.
Huh...?
Why would a disgusting man come here?
What a damn pest.
The only one who can come here
is Nezuko!
I am going to kill you.
Where is Nezuko?
How would I know?
So...
Die!
Do not come...!
Is someone in trouble?
What's happened?
How have they connected
and their spiritual cores not been destroyed yet?
Ah well... that's fine.
They've given me enough time.
Not here.
Although, there is a very faint strange smell.
What is this feeling?
As if I'm covered with a film?
The faint smell of a demon coming from all sides.
But there is no way to determine the location.
I have to get out as soon as possible!
Nezuko is bleeding.
If everyone else fell asleep too
it means the situation is very bad.
What to do?
Could it be...  I'm not using Total Concentration Breathing?
Am I just asleep now?
Tanjiro.
Raise your sword.
The things that must be cut are already here.
Must be... here.
In order to wake up
what do i have to cut?
I think I know.
But, in case you get it wrong
what happened in the dream
if it affects reality
will be irreparable.
Do not hesitate.
Hands on!
Just do it!
Death in dreams can be connected to sobriety in reality!
In other words
I must do this!
Cut... your neck!
I'm fine, I'm still alive.
Nezuko, are you okay?
Nezuko.
Zenitsu.
Inosuke.
Rengoku.
Who are these people?
Tied our wrists with a rope?
Rope.
How is this...
The rope was burned.
Did Nezuko burn the rope?
There's a faint smell of a demon.
Is this smell also on the ticket?
As I thought.
There is also the faint smell of a demon on it.
I must have been hypnotized when the ticket was cut.
This ticket was touch by a demon.
Such a subtle smell.
What could perform such a powerful Blood Arts technique?
What has happened here?
I think it's best to not use a sword for this.
To burn this rope.
Nezuko, please.
Help everyone by burning the ropes!
Zenitsu, wake up!
Wake up, Zenitsu!
Wake up quickly!
Wake up quickly, Inosuke, please!
Inosuke!
Great job.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Nezuko you're doing very well.
They still can't wake up.
What do I do?
Rengo-
What are you doing?
Is this girl controlled by a demon?
Don't try to stop me!
I blame you people for coming!
Stopping me from having a good dream!
She is voluntarily...
This person too.
Why are you still in a daze?
If you're awake, hurry up and help!
I don't care if you're sick or whatever!
If you don't do things well
I'm going to tell that-
Tell him not to let you dream!
Did you hear me?
Was he the one tied to me?
Tuberculosis.
He is sick.
Really bad, too.
I can't forgive this demon.
Taking this opportunity to control people.
Sorry.
I must leave you right now.
You wanted to stay in a happy dream, I know.
I know.
I also wanted to stay in my dream.
Even if it was a dream.
I thought
as long as I can escape the pain caused by my illness
it doesn't matter if I hurt people.
But in your dream
it was so warm.
You should be the embodiment of this person's soul.
It is very clear and transparent, it feels so comfortable.
This is the spiritual core?
Why bring me here?
You know i'm looking for this?
Did you bring me here?
How could this be?
I'm here to destroy the spiritual core.
Why?
Those shining souls in your heart.
Illuminated my painful and twisted heart.
Did I help you?
Thank you.
You must be careful.
Right.
Nezuko!
Such a strong smell.
So heavy.
In such a strong wind,
the smell of this demon is still so strong.
I can still fall asleep in this state.
Although the carriage is indeed a confined space.
I can't believe it
I'm so useless.
The demon is upwind.
Is he in the front carriage?
Nezuko, don't follow me!
It's dangerous outside, stay inside!
Wake everyone up!
Oh, you woke up.
Good morning!
If only you stayed asleep.
Is it this guy...?
Why wake up?
I made you have such a wonderful dream.
If I feel like it
I could also make you dream
of your family being murdered.
Do you prefer to have that kind of dream?
I don't think so, it's too painful.
Then this time
I will let you have it. Your father's dream
of coming back from the dead is over.
Actually, I...
I like to make people have pleasant dreams.
Then the nightmare will follow.
I like to see human beings in pain.
Their distorted expressions.
I can't stop.
Seeing those being crushed by misfortune.
The poor guy struggling with pain.
It's so fascinating.
However, I won't be careless.
Even if it takes a little more work
I will definitely kill you demon slayers.
The ink of those tickets were mixed with my blood.
As long as the Conductor is checking
cuts the ticket and leaves a gap
it will automatically start the process.
But it's weird.
Why did this one wake up?
He saw through the technique in such a short time.
Don't you want to have pleasant dreams?
Have the dreams you want?
Human desire in this respect
is obviously very strong.
Don't enter into someone else's heart without permission!
I can't spare you!
He has earrings on his ears?
I am blessed with good fortune!
He was delivered to me so soon!
Like in a dream.
Soon I can have more...
more of the blood bestowed by Master Muzan!
Then after I become stronger
I can request to take part in the battle to replace a Waxing Moon!
Water Breathing!
Tenth Form!
Perpetual Cycle of Death and Rebirth!
Blood Arts!
Whispers of Forced Unconscious Hypnosis!
Go to sleep.
He's not asleep?
Go to sleep!
How could this be?
Are my Blood Arts not effective?
No, this one has fallen asleep several times.
This one has undergone my hypnosis many times.
The moment he was hypnotized
I could see my Blood Arts were effective.
Killing yourself to stay awake.
Although in a dream
doing such a thing
to kill oneself
requires a lot of courage.
This kid
he is not an ordinary person.
Why is brother not coming to save us?
When our family was killed
what were you doing?
Only brother survived.
What would I want with you
you trash.
Why didn't you die as well?
How can you even live with yourself?
My family would never say such things!
Don't mess with me!
You are not allowed to insult my family!
I didn't feel my blade hit him?
Is this also a dream?
Is this demon weaker than him?
Master said,
"Kill the Pillar and the one who wears
hanafuda earrings."
Master's mood at that time...
...I understand it very well now!
As long as you exist
this fact alone
makes people very angry!
He's not dead
Your expression is amazing!
What I want to see most is your expression!
"I clearly cut off his head, why can't he die?"
You want me to give you a reason.
Okay!
I happen to be very excited.
I'm in a very good mood.
The reason why is so simple
even a baby could understand.
My original body is long gone.
Long gone.
This body is talking to you now
and although it has the shape of a head
it is not the real head.
While you were lying down and sleeping
I merged with this train!
Everything about this train has become my body!
My meat!
My bones!
Look at your expression.
I should understand.
In other words
more than two-hundred passengers on this train
have all become food that will strengthen my body.
They are all my hostages.
Can you protect them?
You are alone.
This train runs from front to back.
So many innocent passengers.
How would you feel handing them all over to me?
What do I do?
I can only protect passengers in two carriages at most.
No amount of strength can guarantee everyone’s safety.
Rengoku, Zenitsu, Inosuke!
Stop sleeping!
Please wake up, please!
Nezuko!
You have to protect those who are asleep!
Men, come with me!
Look at me!
Explosive awakening!
The boar is advancing by leaps and bounds, Lord Inosuke is here!
Inosuke!
No place on this train is safe!
We want to protect those who fell asleep!
The whole train has completely turned into a demon!
Did you hear that?
This whole train is a demon!
I knew it.
Exactly as I expected.
The Master is very wise!
It's so wise to say nothing!
Beast Breathing!
Fifth Fang!
Crazy Cutting!
Whether it's this guy or that guy
I will save them!
You all have a chance!
Worship me!
Your Lord, your Lord
Lord Inosuke!
Coming through!
I have to save the passengers too.
Since Inosuke is here now
I'll go ahead.
This is what things have come to.
Water Breathing!
First Form!
Surface Slash!
My attack had little effect.
The demon's body goes on endlessly.
I have to stop it.
The feeling of demon slayers
running around in my own body.
I can’t believe that I will regenerate immediately.
It won't stop until you are exhausted.
My body slowly...
...attracts hundreds of passengers to eat up!
Thunder Breathing!
First Form!
Thunderclap and Flash!
Do not worry.
Nezuko, I will protect you.
Protect...
Was that thunder I heard?
Is it in the back carriages?
What is the situation of the front?
Is Rengoku awake?
Where are you Rengoku, where are you Nezuko?
I'm useless without knowing where they are.
This isn't good,
what should I do?
We need everyone working together!
The passengers in the last car should be fine, right?
Damn it, this place is too small!
I can't even swing my sword properly!
I took a nap
and look what happened.
I didn't expect it, I didn't expect it.
My Pillar is really useless...
If there's a hole
I would really like to go in!
What was that?
What happened just now?
Was that the demon?
Novice swordsman!
Rengoku!
Before coming here
I used a flurry of attacks against the demon.
It will take some time for the demon to regenerate.
There is not much time, so I will make a long story short.
Yes.
The train has eight carriages.
I'll protect the five carriages behind.
The remaining three sections
are protected by the yellow-haired boy and your sister.
You and the boar-head boy
pay attention to the condition of the three military compartments.
Find the demon's neck.
Neck?
But this demon is already-
No matter what shape it becomes
As long as he is a demon, he has a neck!
I will fight while looking for his vitals.
You have to cheer up!
He's so powerful.
That was just now...
The shaking was caused by Rengoku when he moved?
The situation was so quickly grasped and judged.
One person, responsible for five carriages.
Now is not the time to admire him, idiot!
Hurry up and do what must be done!
The smell is getting stronger and stronger!
I have to hurry!
Inosuke!
Inosuke, where are you?
So noisy!
I'll kill you again!
Above me?
Mr. Big Eyes trying to order me around!
But he seems...
...he seems
...seems very powerful!
Infuriating!
Inosuke!
We have to pay attention to the three cars ahead!
I know!
And i have found!
Found it long ago!
Relying on myself
I found the key to this master!
You found it?
The key is really ahead?
Yes, just ahead!
It's here in the front!
Because the wind is too strong, the smell is blown away.
It's hard for me to detect where it is.
Since Inosuke said so, he must not be wrong.
Near the coal pile!
I know!
Fine, let's go!
Go ahead!
Right here?
Great!
Inosuke!
Suspicious.
Especially near where-
What do you want to do?
G-g-get out!
The demon's neck.
Demon.
Demon's critical spot!
What in the-
What the-
Too many hands!
Bad!
Water Breathing!
Fourth Form!
Striking Tide!
Inosuke, are you okay?
I was not saved just because of you.
I know that.
This...
Directly below...
Directly below here.
The smell is very strong.
Inosuke, the ghost's neck is under here!
Don't order me
I'm your boss!
I know that!
Watch closely.
Beast Breathing!
Second Form!
Rip and Tear!
Is the bone...?
Is that the bones of the neck?
Water Breathing!
Eighth Form!
Waterfall Basin!
Blocked!
The incision healed quickly.
He regenerates quickly.
And
trying my best
I barely saw his bones.
You have to cut it off.
Inosuke!
We're going to continuously attack
with our breathing forms!
One person cuts the meat forward first.
The other cuts off the bone immediately after.
This could work.
Your method sounds like it will work,
I'll make sure to praise you for this!
Thank you!
Let's start.
Blood Arts...
Eyes of Forced Unconscious Sleep.
This is Blood Arts!
I'm going to fall asleep.
Inosuke, cut your neck in his dream
so you can wake up!
Nothing?
If you beat him with that trick, you can beat his spell!
Stupid!
Close your eyes immediately after you wake up!
Otherwise, you'll go back to where you started.
Good, I woke up.
The moment I wake up
the demon's eyes will be waiting for me!
Keep your eyes closed when you wake up!
I want to close my eyes!
Not fast enough!
Faster!
Even faster!
Chop the neck!
Chop...
Faster!
Wake up!
This is not a dream, this is reality!
Don't be fooled by his trap!
Don't be stupid, don't lose your life in vain!
The Lord wears the headpiece of the master on the mountain.
They're so horrible.
They dare not look into my eyes at all!
Blind eyes, full of hate!
He's right.
Where is Inosuke looking?
It's hard to tell.
Anyways,
I just need to chop this guy's head off.
Inosuke!
You won't stop me from dreaming!
Did he stab you?
I'm fine.
Why bother with that bastard?
No, we can't let him die.
Hurry up and cut off the demon's neck!
We can't hold out for much longer!
I know.
Move fast.
Inosuke.
Breathe well.
We'll cut off the demon's neck together.
Keep attacking.
This is bad.
If I fall asleep now.
Hateful!
I'm going to rush him, watch my back!
Beast Breathing!
Third Fang!
Devour!
Please bless me.
Dad, please bless me.
Let me chop off the bones with one blow.
Let me chop off the bones with one blow!
Dance of the Fire God!
Clear Blue Sky!
What a scream, and the shaking!
It's going to roll over, Inosuke!
Wait, is your stomach okay?
Inosuke, protect passengers!
I can't die.
If i die,
that person will become a murderer.
I can't die.
I don't want anyone to die.
Are you okay? Santaro?
Cheer me up!
This demon's body is too elastic and became a meat pad.
But we're saved!
Is your stomach okay?
Is the stabbed belly okay?
I don't care.
How about Inosuke?
The Lord is full of vitality, not even a small cold!
I can't move yet.
Hurry up and save the others.
I wonder if anyone was injured?
Near the demon's neck... where is the driver?
I think it's best that guy died.
That's not good at all.
He's the one who stabbed you in the stomach!
That guy's foot was pinched by the train,
he can't move at all.
His feet are squashed and he can't move at all.
Leave it alone.
In this case
he has been punished enough.
Hurry and save him.
Please.
I'm going.
Who told me to be your boss?
I did it because my men begged me.
After saving the others
I'm going to pull out all of his hair.
You don't have to do that.
It looks like the Sun is about to dawn.
I need to adjust my breathing.
You have to rescue the injured quickly.
Nezuko, Zenitsu, Rengoku.
I'm sure they'll be alright.
My body is disintegrated, there is no way to regenerate.
Did I lose? Am I going to die?
Me?
How is this possible...?
I haven't tried my best!
I haven't even eaten a human.
Integrate with the train.
An excellent plan to devour a large number of humans at once.
All for nothing!
I am like this now,
when I spent so much effort and time...
It's that guy.
It's that guy!
I was holding the life of priceless hostages.
But I'm still ruled by others!
He controls everything.
Is this the power of a Hashira?
That kid.
That kid is moving so fast.
Obviously, the sleep technique has not completely subsided.
And the girl.
Isn't she a demon?
What happened?
How can a demon partner with a demon slayer?
Why was she not killed by Master?
I hate...
To put it plainly,
it's all the fault of that kid who figured out my technique.
That made me feel bad.
It's that kid's fault.
Anyway,
even if you can only kill that kid.
There's also that boar.
If there was only that kid, I would have killed him.
I blame the boar.
His instinct is so sensitive.
He is really sensitive to sight.
Am I going to lose? Am I going to die?
This is a nightmare, it must be a nightmare!
Killed by the demon slayers!
It's always the the bottom of the barrel.
Thinking about it...
in this century
are all demons with familiar faces
who have defeated countless Pillars in the Demon Slayer Corp.
Are these the opponents of the Waxing Moons?
Is the strength of the Waxing Moons
from a different dimension?
I have accumulated so much blood,
and yet still far behind the Waxing Moons.
I really want to start all over again.
How could there be such a miserable nightmare.
It seems that you have learned to concentrate on your breathing.
Admirable.
Rengoku.
Learning to stay in school is the first step to becoming a Pillar.
Before becoming a Pillar,
you may have ten thousand steps to go.
I will work hard.
Your abdomen is bleeding heavily.
Focus.
Improve the accuracy of your breathing.
Concentrate on carrying your breath to every part of your body.
Don't forget the blood vessels.
To repair broken blood vessels.
Strengthen concentration.
Right there.
Stop the bleeding quickly, you must stop the bleeding.
Focus.
The bleeding has stopped.
As long as you can master the breathing methods
you can do things ordinary people can't do.
Although not everything can be done.
But it does make you
become stronger than yesterday's self.
I understand.
Everyone is safe.
Although there are many injured,
none of their injuries are life-threatening.
You don't need to be strong now, take a good rest.
Thank you very much.
A Waxing Moon.
Why is it here?
Flame Breathing!
Second Form!
Rising Scorching Sun!
What an excellent sword.
He regenerates quickly.
This strong of a sense of oppression...
This is a Waxing Moon.
I can not understand
why you chose to attack the injured person first?
Because I think he will prevent me from talking to you.
Just like this.
What can I say to you?
Although this is the first time we have met
I am already annoyed.
Is that so?
I also hate weak humans the most.
Seeing useless people makes me sick.
It looks like you and me
have completely different standards and values.
Let me give you a wonderful proposal.
Do you want to join us as a demon?
Of course not.
I know at a glance
that power
are you a Hashira?
Your abilities have been tempered
close to the highest level.
I am the Flame of the Nine Pillars.
My name is Kyojuro Rengoku.
I am Akaza.
Kyojuro, let me tell you
why you missed the gate
unable to step into the highest realm.
Because you are human.
Because you will grow old, because you will die.
Become a demon, Kyojuro.
In this way
whether it's a hundred years or two-hundred years
you can keep improving, you can become stronger.
Among all the demons I have encountered so far
his smell is closest to Kibutsuji Muzan.
I have to get up,
I have to support Rengoku.
Aging and the declining towards death
is what makes a short-lived creature like a human
beautiful.
Precisely because people will grow old, precisely because people will die
talent will always be so lovely and noble.
So-called "power"
is not an adjective that only applies to the physical.
This boy is not weak at all.
Do not insult him.
I can say it as many times as needed.
Your standards are completely different from mine.
No matter how many reasons you give me
I will not be a demon.
Is that so?
Blood Arts!
Technique Development!
Destructive Death: Compass Needle!
Since you don't want to be a demon, you should ready yourself.
I can't see their movements.
Among the Pillars I have killed so far
no one was a Flame Pillar.
And no one agreed to become a demon...
my invitation.
Why on Earth would you deny the invitation?
I am also pursuing the highest state of martial arts.
I really can't understand.
Obviously only those who are selected can become demons.
Looking at people with perfect talent.
Becoming ugly with age.
It's so sad.
Just die, Kyojuro.
While you are young and strong.
Destructive Death: Air!
That's it.
Flame Breathing!
Fourth Form!
Blooming Flame Undulation!
Throwing his fists through the air
he can attack me
at a speed the fraction of an instant.
If we fight at this distance
it will be difficult to cut him.
In that case.
I'll be close!
Perfect speed.
Such superb swordsmanship is disappearing from the world!
Kyojuro!
Don't you feel sad?
It won't be sad
because it is natural for humans to die!
Do not move!
If the wound opens, it will become fatal!
You are there on standby!
Don't care about the weak, Kyojuro!
Use your utmost ability!
Do you think you can beat me?
You really are agile!
Rengoku!
Mr. Big Eyes!
Become a demon, Kyoujuro.
In this way, you and me can fight forever.
Improve each other's abilities.
You have the qualifications to fight with me.
I reject your offer.
Ask me again, I dare you.
I will never be a demon.
Flame Breathing!
Third Form!
Fiery Spirits!
That's great!
You really are dangerous!
Keep going!
No flaws, no way to intervene.
It's so fast that I can't keep up.
Those two are fighting in a different dimension.
If you break in
there's no way you'd survive.
Even if you wanted to help
that would just be a disservice.
So I dare not move at all.
Rengoku.
Haven't you figured it out yet?
If you keep attacking me
it means you've chosen your own death.
Kyojuro!
Flame Breathing!
First Form!
Unknowing Fire!
What a pity to kill you here!
You haven’t even reached your peak!
Second Form!
Rising Scorching Sun!
One or two years from now
your moves will be more refined
their lethality will also increase.
Third Form!
Fiery Spirits!
Fourth Form!
Blooming Flame Undulation!
Destructive Death!
Fifth Form!
Flame Tiger!
Disorder!
Kyojuro!
Did it succeed? Did you beat him?
Will noth...
How could this be?
Keep fighting with me.
Don't die, Kyojuro.
Rengoku.
Rengoku!
Even if you fight with the determination to sacrifice yourself.
Everything is in vain, Kyojuro.
That superb slash you inflicted.
No matter how fierce.
The wound can heal in an instant.
But look at yourself.
The left eye is completely ruined and the ribs are almost shattered.
Internal organs are also damaged.
Usually those injuries are impossible to recover from.
But if you are a demon
those injuries can be recovered at a glance.
This kind of injury is just a small scratch to the demon.
No matter how hard you struggle
humans cannot defeat demons.
I really want to help.
My hands are feet just won't move.
Although my condition is not separate from my injuries
after using the Dance of the Fire God, I will be like this.
Kyojuro, you...
I will...
I will perform my duty well.
Everyone here!
None of them will die!
It must be done in an instant.
Destroy him completely.
Flame Breathing!
Ninth Form!
What incredible power!
To have such serious injuries
and still show perfect resolve!
Such spiritual power!
There is no flaw in the posture.
You think you are above being a demon, Kyojuro?
Let us fight each other forever!
Burn!
Burn beyond your limits!
I am the Pillar of Flame!
Rengoku Kyojuro!
Ninth Form!
Rengoku!
Destructive Death: Annihilation!
See.
Rengoku!
You will die!
You will really die, Kyojuro!
Be a demon!
Say you are going to be a demon!
You are one of the few selected!
Kyojuro.
Yes, Mother.
You have to think carefully
about Mother's next question.
You know yourself.
Why are you born stronger than others?
I do not know.
To help those weaker than yourself.
You were born blessed.
Someone who has more talent than others.
That power
must be used selflessly.
Make good use of it for others.
Take advantage of the power granted by Heaven.
To hurt others
is not allowed.
Help the weak.
Anytime, anywhere.
It’s your job to be strong.
You have to take responsibility.
That is your mission to be carried out.
You must not forget this.
Yes.
I'm afraid I don't have much time left.
To be the mother of a strong and kind child
makes me very happy.
I wish you well, son.
Mother!
To think I could have a Mother like you!
I feel very honored!
Blocked?
What unbelievable power!
My right hand has penetrated his vital organs!
Oh no, it's almost dawn!
I have to kill him and leave this place!
I can't pull out my hand!
You will not escape!
No matter what Rengoku will call me afterwards
I have to do it!
I have to cut off his neck!
Faster!
Dawn...!
The sun will shine soon!
I must run away quickly!
I will never let you go
until your neck is cut off!
Get off of me!
Inosuke, move quickly!
Move for Rengoku!
Beast Breathing!
First Fang!
Pierce!
I have to get away from the Sun immediately!
This is bad!
I must be as far away from the Sun as possible!
Don't run away!
Don't run away, you bastard!
What kind of nonsense is that?
Isn't there a brain in his head?
I didn't run away because of you or the demon slayers.
I ran away to escape the Sun!
What's more, the outcome has already been decided!
That guy will run out of strength and die soon!
No matter where you go
the Demon Slayer Corp. will always be there!
Fight in the darkness
that's the only place you can fight!
We are flesh and blood!
Our wounds cannot heal easily
and it's impossibe to recover your hands and feet!
You are not allowed to run, you bastard!
You wicked, despicable creature!
Compared to guys like you
Rengoku is far greater!
Far greater than you!
Rengoku did not lose!
He didn't let anyone on the train die!
He fought to the end and successfully protected everyone!
You lost!
Rengoku defeated you!
Stop screaming so loudly.
The wound in your stomach will open.
Your injury is not minor.
Novice swordsman, if you die
it means that I lose the battle.
Rengoku.
Come to me.
I have something to tell you.
I remembered something.
I remembered when I dreamed of the past.
Of the home where I was born.
You can go there if you wish.
There is a collection of notes left by Flame swordsman of the past.
My father used to read those notes.
Because i haven't seen it
I don't know the exact contents.
What you told me earlier
about the God of Destruction, Kagura.
Maybe there will be records in those notes.
Rengoku, please stop talking like this.
Please use breathing to stop the bleeding!
Is there no way to make the wound heal?
No.
I will die soon.
I'll talk as long as I can.
Just listen.
Please tell my brother Senjuro
Ask him to do what he wants.
Move on the path you feel right.
This is my wish.
Tell my Father.
I hope he can take care of his health.
Also, mountain boy.
Also, boy with the box.
I am willing to believe you.
I agree that she is a member of the Demon Slayer Corp.
When I was on the train
I saw the girl bleeding
working hard to protect mankind.
Risking her life to fight demons.
She protects humanity.
No matter what others say.
Your sister is part of the Demon Slayer Corp.
Stand tall and live.
Regardless of your own weaknesses.
No matter how hard you are hit.
Burn in your heart.
Grit your teeth and move forward.
Even if you stop and rest.
The flow of time will not stop for you.
Time can't accompany you to bear grief.
Don't let my death fall too heavily upon you.
I am a Pillar.
I am a shield for younger generations.
I am a Pillar
and any of them would have made the same choice.
I can't let the younger generation fail.
Red-haired boy.
Boarhead boy
Yellow-haired boy.
You must continue to grow.
Believe in the near future.
You are the future of the Demon Slayers.
I trust you.
I trust you from the bottom of my heart.
Mother?
Have I done it?
Things I should do, things I have to practice?
Did I do it all?
You did very well.
When the train derailed
Rengoku used many techniques.
He did his best to damage the carriage
and minimize the harm to humans.
That's right.
How could such a person die?
Did a Waxing Moon really show up?
Why did a Waxing Moon come here?
Are they really that powerful?
How could...
Why is it...
when you're close to completing your mission,
right in front of you,
another high wall appears.
Novice swordsmen, all powerful,
all killed and fought in far-away places.
And yet I still don't have the ability to go there.
I'm stuck in this place!
Can I become a strong man like Rengoku?
Don't say such discouraging words!
No one cares if you can be like him!
Don't talk about this kind of nonsense!
Since he said he believed in you!
In addition to his trust,
there's no reason to think about these things!
The dead creatures just return to the dust!
Even if you are crying
he won't come back!
Don't cry, even if you're not reconciled!
No matter how miserable, no matter how humiliated!
We must all continue to live!
Aren't you crying too?
Crying until tears came out of your headpiece?
The Lord did not cry!
Come over and train!
Rengoku is gone.
The Waxing Moons.
Even Rengoku was no match?
I do not believe it.
Namo Amitabha
Aku bersumpah mereka akan dihancurkan.
Setan yang menjijikkan.
Apakah begitu?
Dua ratus penumpang di kereta
dan tidak ada yang meninggal.
Kyojuro bekerja sangat keras.
Dia adalah anak yang luar biasa.
Saya tidak akan kesepian.
Lagi pula, saya tidak punya banyak waktu tersisa.
Segera saya akan melihat Kyojuro,
dan Tanah Musim Semi yang Kekal.
Rengoku ...!